[Music]
My decree Kaviyani Daridiyat Nikalsi I am
always in the blood I have not read the
poetry Very intelligent in my class Always
top
[Music]
Mukul Bhai in the big city
This was the right time A pearl amount was received
ICICI Prudential prosperity was given its
due time This was the time
Tamara Mota dream had the government karishons with
ICICI Prudential prosperity with a water
[Music] The
policy was matured there then tax
free money Mani Jash Jis Tave Tamara Madonna
bright future met there
[Music] Stay
safe,
meet yours with ICICI Prudential prosperity
ji apetam ne returns ki puri guaranty
Your dream is with you Adopt a
trustworthy ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance
[Music]